{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-15",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 15",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "grade5",
    "unit15",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 15: Our health",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "matter",
      "answer": "vấn đề",
      "speak": "matter"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "headache",
      "answer": "đau đầu",
      "speak": "headache"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "toothache",
      "answer": "đau răng",
      "speak": "toothache"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "sore throat",
      "answer": "viêm họng, đau họng",
      "speak": "sore throat"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "stomach ache",
      "answer": "đau bụng",
      "speak": "stomach ache"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "tired",
      "answer": "mệt mỏi",
      "speak": "tired"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "advice",
      "answer": "lời khuyên",
      "speak": "advice"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "rest",
      "answer": "sự nghỉ ngơi",
      "speak": "rest"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "medicine",
      "answer": "thuốc",
      "speak": "medicine"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "salt water",
      "answer": "nước muối",
      "speak": "salt water"
    }
  ]
}